It's one of those deals that uh you
know, it hit me Friday night. It was
kind of going around. I think our little
boy gave it to gave it to my wife first
and then uh and then got me pretty good
and
um you know, I feel good though. It was
you know, just wanted to be able to be
smart not get give ourselves a chance of
giving it to anybody else cuz of how
contagious this can be and hopefully I
didn't um but you know, with passing out
game balls trying to do the the fist
pump as much as you can. It's you
realize how out of norm it is for me.
I'm a big hugger and
um so hopefully I feel better and and uh
you know, can get back to being the
normal with these guys cuz you know, I
uh I don't like this. Did you feel okay
on the sideline? Yeah, I felt okay.
Yeah, I I felt good. I mean, if I was I
don't want to get too descriptive with
you but we fought through it and uh you
know, ultimately the guys did a great
job. Really proud of them and you know,
I think this is a cool reflection of the
coaching staff in general too and um it
was [clears throat] a good step in the
right direction and you know, now we got
to get continue to build on this. You
guys have run pretty well all season but
just could you describe just the past
two weeks, what's taken this group to
the the level it's at right now?
As far as you talking about just the run
game? Yeah, I I just think guys are
executing. You know, I think the runners
are really running hard. I think they're
pressing it. They're understanding
exactly what the intent is. You know, I
think Kyren and Blake do a great job.
Got to give a lot of credit to Ron Gould
um and then also I think you know, the
offensive line obviously has been key
and critical and it's the offensive
line. It's the tight ends. It's the
receivers. The run game takes all 11.
You know, Matthew getting us in and out
of the right looks and so I think we're
getting connected. I think we're able to
have a little bit of diversity in terms
of some of the different things whether
it be personnel or run schemes, you
know, where you can go direct downhill
or you can be able to stretch people a
little bit.
So um they came out in a lighter
grouping on us today uh when we were in
our 13 personnel and I thought it was
really good that we were able to
establish the run the way we were and um
you have to be able to do those types of
things but I've been really pleased with
it, Nate. We got to continue to build on
it but you know, like I mentioned about
Ron, you know, I think Ryan Windell
deserves a ton of credit. Uh obviously
the players are bringing it to life and
then Scooter Off with the tight ends and
and you know, Yarbs always gets those
guys playing their ass off at receiver
as well.
Yeah, no, they were for uh they were for
artists.
>> [laughter]
>> I thought he played excellent. I thought
he did a great job of you know,
distributing the ball. I thought he made
some big-time throws um and I thought he
did a great job of when there was some
you know, pressure being able to keep
the ball in play, not take negatives. I
think you want to stay ahead of the
sticks against a group like this. They
do a good job when they get into some of
their sub rushes and um I thought
Matthew was outstanding [clears throat]
um you know, and and I don't necessarily
think the numbers always can reflect
that. Um you know, it was cool to see
him get another three touchdowns but he
was great. I thought he saw the field
really well. I thought he threw the ball
with accuracy and anticipation and then
uh you know, to Nate's question, a lot
of the stuff in the run game was a real
credit to Matthew getting us in and out
of some of the right looks and he's been
outstanding. He's he's doing a hell of a
job. I'm happy for him. You guys have
not faced a lot of third downs the last
two weeks. What does that show about how
your offense Well, it shows how
important it is about the early down
efficiency. You know, I mean, last week
was was really rare. Obviously we had
some of the turnovers. It was good to
have a clean slate um in that regard
this week but you know, when you can be
efficient on those early downs, you
eliminate a lot of those pass situations
where the defense feels like they can
almost get the pen in their hand and so
um for us to be able to be the the
offense that we want to be, we got to
continue to take steps in that direction
and to be able to have the balance run
and pass like we've had in the early
down efficiency, that's always key and
critical. Sean, all three losses this
year, you guys have really came back
very strong
>> Yeah.
Is that something you sensed today or
did you It is. It's something I sensed.
You know, I thought the guys did a great
job. This is this is a mentally tough
group. This is a resilient group. Um you
know, you got to earn it and and I
thought they had a great week of
preparation. I thought even just the
maturity of even some of the stuff where
I wasn't around a little bit just
because of what I was dealing with, just
the way they handled it. These are grown
men, you know, and they do such a great
job of This is a player-led team um and
and really I can't say enough about what
a great job our coaches do. I don't mean
that to be minimizing them at all but um
we got a lot of really great leaders in
that locker room um and I think they
take the ownership, the initiative of
what we want to be about and and how you
ultimately want to be able to respond,
not react when we do have some of those
setbacks and this is exactly in
alignment with what we wanted and now we
got to continue to build on it.
>> And just to follow up on on what Nate
said on the running game, it is all 11.
How do you see
Blake and Kyren
Well, I think it's that. I think they
are complementing each other. I think
they're doing a great job. You know,
they're obviously they're similar but
they have some different skill sets.
They're both excellent backs that have
great ownership and understanding of
what we're trying to get done. I think
them being able to play off of one
another allows them to just be fresher
as the season and as games go on and you
could see. I mean, you know, Blake pops
the 48-yarder. It's a great job for us
being able to get the removal and it
opens up a backside cut um and then he's
got the juice to be able to finish it
but I think Kyren's been excellent. I
just think they do a great job of
supporting one another um and I think
the fact that when you have two guys
that you can trust as much as them, um
they're going to be stronger, they're
going to be fresher because this is a
long season that we go through. How
would you describe the impact Puka had
today? He's outstanding. You know, he he
was he was great. I thought the two big
in-cuts that he caught early on in the
game on back-to-back plays were big. Um
you know, they really got us going um
and and he's you know, to be able to win
on the double move, um some of the
catches that he's making where you know,
he's it's a contested catch but then
he's pulling guys in uh to be able to
score. He's a freaking stud. Love Puka.
All right. Thank you guys.
>> Uh it's fun. I um I have great
teammates.
Only reason anybody's saying something
like that about me is cuz all those guys
in there are so I'm appreciative. I love
going to work with those guys and
it's fun.
I don't play the game for that. You
know, I play the game for those guys in
there and and the respect to those guys
and the guys that we compete against,
but it's cool.
Your first This team's first four
touchdowns were were different guys. Can
you speak to the balance of this team
[clears throat] and and how that helps
you?
Yeah, we should have a fifth. I should
have hit Tay on that fade, too. So,
want that one back bad. He crushed him.
But, uh
No, it was good. I mean, I think
when we're at our best, we're kind of
dictating the terms and and spreading
the ball around.
Thought we had a great plan coming into
the day. Obviously, executed it really
well
in and out of the huddle.
Great communication and then our guys up
front, I mean, they they own the line of
scrimmage.
And when you do that, we got skill guys
that can uh you know, make people pay
and
just proud and happy for those guys up
front for the way they played. How did
you see it helping to have the one-two
running back punch today?
Well, I think both those guys can do
everything we ask, you know, and and
that's the coolest part is, you know,
whoever's in the game and Ronnie really
ran it great at the end of the game,
too. You know, I got total trust and
confidence in all those three guys to
run any play we have in our offense.
There's no, "Hey, this guy's in, we got
to do this. That guy's in, we got to do
that." No, we just call our offense and
then both those guys you know, feed off
of each other. I mean, they they have
their unique styles of how they run, but
both of them are, you know, playing at a
great clip and obviously had big days
today.
Were you aware of Shawn was not feeling
well and Oh, yeah. How did that impact
his ability at all if at all the
communication? No, it was you know, I
think
it was a great collaboration on the
offensive side of the ball. He wasn't
feeling well the last couple days and
I'm just
proud of the way we all kind of came
together and and attacked this week. I
thought Mike did a hell of a job.
Really, everybody that was involved did
a hell of a job. You
score as many points and and play like
we did on offense today, takes everybody
and
you know, it was it was cool with you
know, our head guy down just a little
bit watching everybody kind of rally and
and you know, do their part and do it a
little bit better and and you know, the
results were good. You and Puka got into
an early groove [snorts] in today. Just
what kind of led to that connection
clicking as well as it did?
You know, I think just opportunities. He
had opportunities and I I tried to put
the ball in a good place and he made
some great plays like he always does.
So, I got total trust in everybody. I
mean,
Puka did that today. It could be anybody
the next day and and that's the fun part
about playing in this offense is uh
you know, wherever the coverage tells me
to go with the football, you know, I'm
going to try and go there with it and
just missed on a couple with Tay today.
You know, I had some big ones to the
tight ends. They were great in the
keeper game, too. So,
I don't know. Puka's, you know, a hell
of a football player, great player for
our team. We're happy that uh
you know, he's he's with us and you
know, he showed it again today. Some of
these Puka catches are acrobatic or
one-handed. [snorts]
At this point, does anything he do
surprise you or are you just kind of
used to No, I appreciate the hell out of
all of them. You know, I mean, it's it's
cool to watch him do his thing. He's a
physical player. Just try to put him in
some good spots for him and he does
unbelievable stuff, you know, coming
down with the football, contested
catches.
You know, so I I don't say that I
wouldn't say I'm surprised, but I do
appreciate all of them. I don't sit
there and take them for granted, that's
for sure.
Next up is Lions, which is
You you have history there. How does it
feel to be playing so well
going into that
>> [snorts]
>> divisional match? I mean, uh
you hate to, you know, hate to hear it,
but we got to earn it every single week,
you know? And and cuz I played well this
week doesn't mean, you know, you're
guaranteed to play well the next week.
We got to go earn that. We do it every
single week. I got a ton of respect for
that team. Um head coach, everybody,
they they do a hell of a job and have
done a great job the last couple years.
So, it'll be a big challenge every time
we play these guys. Seems like a good
match. So,
um you know, looking forward to the
opportunity of playing on a
you know, on a big stage against a
really good team. You just saw it a bit
already, but when your run game
[clears throat] is this lethal, I guess
can you explain kind of just the effect
that has when you guys do then call a
pass play over
Yeah, you know, I thought I thought we
were really disciplined, um you know,
how we approached the game. Um they
wanted to run small people out there and
we were in 13 and
you know, it was just
Hey, let's
keep running the rock. And and you know,
we can call all those runs, but if we
don't make them work, you know, then
then, you know, they have the upper
hand. So, a ton of credit to our guys up
front, our tight ends, our backs,
receivers blocking.
Um you know, they were running small
people and we were in 13 and and uh
First couple drives we just ran it
great. So,
um and continued to run it good the rest
of the day. So, uh it goes back to a
little bit of, you know, kind of
dictating the terms and and then uh
you know, even in base defense I thought
we ran it well, too. So, proud of those
guys.
Cool. Thank you.
It's your first game in the NFL with 100
yards. And just what was it like to be
out there and be a part of, you know,
everything that came together on offense
today? Oh, man, it was a you know,
blessing come true, but that's what we
worked on all week. You know, fixing
what we need to fix from, you know, our
loss and we we did that. You know,
starting with the offensive line. I
mean, they did a phenomenal job. And
then when you know, when we're 13
personnel, our tight ends, they're
blocking their tails off and
receivers are blocking and it just
makes, you know, my job, Kyren's job,
you know, a lot easier. And so, man,
it's a a credit to everyone, you know,
the coaches,
Coach Ron G. You know, it's amazing,
man. I love I love playing in the
backfield. Sean really talked about the
running game is really all 11. I don't
want to diminish that when I ask how do
you and Kyren compliment each other? How
do you push each
Uh we love competing. And so, when you
when you love competing and you have a
partner like I do with Kyren, Kyren has
with me, and really just the running
back room in general, you know, we're
all super close. And we all want to see
each other succeed, you know, big time.
And so, you know, when I'm when I'm on
the sideline I see Kyren break off a
run, I get hyped. And that makes me when
I go in, I want I want to break off a
long one just so we can keep feeding off
each other. But, you know, it is all 11
like you said. I mean, Kyren and I
wouldn't be doing any of that if it
wasn't for everyone else. You know what
I'm saying? And so, you know, that's
what you love about the game of
football. It's truly a team sport. And
you know, that's why, you know, we
started playing at 6 and, you know, it's
by the grace of God we're still playing.
You have you've had some runs where it
seemed like you were maybe one step, one
you know, move away from
breaking a really long one for a
touchdown. What was that like today to
get past that and run for that daylight?
Yeah, man, it it definitely was a lot of
fun. You know, definitely something I've
been wanting to do and feel like I've
been super close. You know, the block
the line have has blocked it really well
a couple times and it was just up to me
to, you know, finish the play off, but
you know, you just go back to work, you
know? Coach always talks about how the
work works. And you know, I go back to
work with the guys. I go back to work
with, you know, Coach G and my team and,
you know, it paid off today, but
uh you know, the day is over now, you
know? Now it's on to the next, you know
what I'm saying? We still have a lot of
football ahead of us and, you know, I'm
excited to see how much better we can
actually get cuz we can get a lot
better. With Sean sick, he complimented
the job that the offensive staff did in
his
What did you see yesterday as preparing
for the game
with how everyone else stepped up?
Leaders. You know, leaders. And I that's
what that's what I love, you know, about
this organization, right? We have such a
great leader in Coach McVay, but you
know, right right underneath of him, you
know, Coach LaFleur, Coach Shead, you
know, Coach Yarbs, Coach Ron G, you
know, everyone's a leader in their own
way and they know how to,
you know, handle things when, you know,
Coach McVay wasn't able to be there.
Right? The culture remains the same, the
team remains the same. I mean, you know,
we don't you know, we don't budge. You
know, we just
work around it and uh man, they they did
a phenomenal job at making sure, you
know, myself and the guys were ready to
go out there and compete today and, you
know, Coach Sean as
as I know he would, it would, you know,
show up even if he wasn't feeling well.
That he staff hasn't [clears throat] had
a lot of holding run games play with
Rodgers long career. So, just how does
it feel to be a part of giving that
opportunity to have it? How do you see
him maybe feed off of it and play even
better with that? I mean, he's he's
amazing. You know, I mean, you you heard
the crowd, you know, MVP MVP. You know,
that's something I believe in. You know,
he might not say it, but I mean, he's
he's a phenomenal quarterback, man. He's
done a phenomenal job this year at just,
you know, leading the team, being that
general field general. Um you know, I
really enjoy playing in the backfield
with him. And you know, just being able
to get the run game going open opens up
everything, you know? Just like, you
know, when you're passing the ball deep,
then it opens up the run, you know? They
just go back and forth and, you know,
when you can play that type of ball like
we were able to go out there and play
today, you know, it's hard to stop. What
was going through your mind as that long
touchdown run was unfolding and when
that play was called? Did you have an
idea that it executed correctly right
away? Yeah, we we had an idea, you know,
the offensive line, you know, Matthew,
Kyren, myself, we talked about, you
know, this play, you know, throughout
the week and where it possibly might hit
and,
you know, a couple runs today hit this
way, that way, you know, they were going
a little bit everywhere, but uh you
know, when I got the handoff and I felt
the defense flow and, you know, the line
was connected kind of
pushing them and I
you know, put my foot in the ground and
hit it. I knew I I knew I needed to
break a long one sooner than
later
you know, kind of slipped a little bit.
And I was able to just, you know, turn
on the jets a little bit, but uh
man, it was uh it was great, man, you
know? All glory to God.
Thank you.
Yeah, I think there's a uptick in our
urgency. Um we always bring the energy.
Uh we always have the focus. Um but I
think we were a little bit more urgent
this week. And that's something that
we're going to look to continue to carry
throughout the rest of the season.
You guys early on, you know, they they
were able to get you in some passing
plays before you settled in. But what do
you feel like
I guess changed for you guys or let you
kind of adjust within the game to to
shut them down? Yeah, I think we were
able to settle in. I think we did a good
job uh all day today being able to knock
out the run. And then we saw, I mean, we
knew they were going to try to get 85
the ball. They have a couple receivers
out. Um and 85 was already their number
one target. So, a couple of those
screens, they did a lot of those
screens. Um and then they were able to
to make some big plays. It's the NFL. Um
everyone's going to be able to make some
plays, but it's about how you respond.
It's about how you play that next snap.
And uh obviously, you know, the a lot of
the first quarter didn't really look
like us or didn't really feel like us
defensively. Uh but we were able to to
turn that around and ultimately, you
know, come out and play the ball like
we're like we're used to playing. Toby,
of all three losses this year, all three
had a lot of self-inflicted wounds. And
next week after all three losses,
you guys played really strong. Mhm.
Did you know that today? Did you know
that earlier this week?
I I I I mean, the amount of confidence
that I have in all of these guys and the
way that you can we came in on Monday.
We had a longer Monday last week. And
you could just see it in the eyes of all
of the guys. You could see it in the way
that each person was, you know, maybe
spending a little bit extra time in the
hot tubs, cold tubs, getting their body
right, a little bit extra time in their
film. Uh really making sure that we were
locked in on our keys. And so, uh we got
to do a better job of not putting
ourselves in that position and carrying
that over each week. But, I think we
have done a really great job of that. I
think the urgency just ticked up just a
little bit more. Um and that's what
again, we're going to look to continue
that for the rest of the season. And we
know what the standard is. The standard
is the standard and we got to hold that
um
you know, hold that standard throughout
the week. What was it like seeing Nate
get that interception and also being
able to punctuate the celebration as
well? Yeah, I know, that was exciting.
You know, you're used to seeing him
force the turnovers in in the form of
punching. Um but, you know, we had a
game going and I turned around and Nate
was dancing with the ball or like
running around with the ball. Um and you
could just see the amount of energy that
all of those guys. Obviously, all of us
guys, we love Nate. He's a great leader.
He's a great player. Um and he just
brings so much positive energy to this
team. And you know, couldn't be prouder
to have him as one of our captains. And
yeah, being able to spike it, I didn't
know I was going to be called to do
that. He was just like, "Spike that."
And I was like, "I guess so." And I
jumped up. I don't know how the form
was. Then I lost the ball and I was
trying to get the ball back to him. I
was like, "He needs the ball. Where did
the ball go?" But, um yeah, could not be
prouder of him. He's playing some really
good ball for us. And he's leading this
team the right way.
Appreciate you guys.
Appreciate it.
After you guys giving up that touchdown
on the first drive, what which changed?
Because it was a
completely different game than that.
Yeah, I think they kind of motivated us.
We know that that was unacceptable. You
know, we just started playing our keys
better. You know, we just locked in but
yeah, give them the first touchdown like
that on the first drive, you know, we
never do stuff like that. So it just
just woke us up. So
something that we needed I feel like.
On those
lines, last week you talked about the
need for a wake-up call
>> [snorts]
>> after Carolina.
How do you feel like guys bought into
that and responded throughout the week
up to today? I definitely think we
responded well. Preparation everything,
attention to our practice and just
reading our keys the right way but I
like the approach that we took and got
the job done. So
Were you worried [snorts] that Shawn was
feeling good while in coverage?
I was worried that last night when we
didn't have a team meeting. I was kind
of worried cuz we always have team
meetings and then we didn't have one
because of that. So I'm glad that you
know, he made a trip in way up there on
the sideline but yeah, I hate to see
that.
You guys are so used to
Nate creating takeaways by punching the
ball out. What was it like seeing him
get the pick and then just the the
celebration you guys all had after? It
was great, man. He works his I don't
want to curse but he works so hard, you
know what I'm saying? He always punches
the ball out and stuff like that and
finally he got the interception that he
was working so hard for, man. It's I
love to see him, you know, be successful
like that. So like celebrating with him,
those are moments that we, you know, we
grind for, we practice for. So it was a
great feeling.
Thank you. Appreciate it.